<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lauren&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lauren&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Lauren Klepac</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Thanks for stopping by. If you have any questions or feedback about anything on here, feel free to reach out to me on Twitter or by email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the 2016 CCES</title>
      <link>/2018/12/30/2019-01-02-cces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/30/2019-01-02-cces/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Cooperative Congressional Election Survey (CCES) is an online survey administred to over 60,000 respondents every 2 years in two waves: pre- and post- the United States Novemeber elections. The survey asks many questions on the respondents’ views on public policy, social issues, and vote choice, and as such is a treasure trove for exploring U.S. public opinion and political behavior. A file with survey responses from voters in the 2016 Presidential election is available for download here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome I have been teaching myself R for a few years, largely through the great resources at DataCamp and other online courses, and working on a few projects on my own. I hope to use this site to share what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned and to connect with and learn from others.
I&amp;rsquo;m a Program Analyst for the Federal Government (views here are entirely my own), and I have a background in health policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My awesome project</title>
      <link>/project/my-awesome-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/my-awesome-project/</guid>
      <description>About project Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>