<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lauren&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lauren&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Lauren Klepac</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping a Senate race with sf and ggplot2</title>
      <link>/2019/02/18/2019-02-18-mapping-a-senate-race-with-sf-and-ggplot2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/18/2019-02-18-mapping-a-senate-race-with-sf-and-ggplot2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I wanted to get some experience mapping with R, so I decided to look at recent election results from my home state of Pennsylvania. First I downloaded results by county from the PA Secretary of State’s website for the 2012 and 2018 Senate races, both of which were won by Democrat Bob Casey.
I created a table in Excel with results from these two races, as well as the FIPS codes for counties in Pennsylvania and read it into R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Thanks for stopping by. If you have any questions or feedback about anything on here, feel free to reach out to me on Twitter or by email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the 2016 CCES</title>
      <link>/2018/12/30/2019-01-02-cces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/30/2019-01-02-cces/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Cooperative Congressional Election Survey (CCES) is an online survey administred to over 60,000 respondents every 2 years in two waves: pre- and post- the United States Novemeber elections. The survey asks many questions on the respondents’ views on public policy, social issues, and vote choice, and as such is a treasure trove for exploring U.S. public opinion and political behavior. A file with survey responses from voters in the 2016 Presidential election is available for download here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome I have been teaching myself R for a few years, largely through the great resources at DataCamp and other online courses, and working on a few projects on my own. I hope to use this site to share what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned and to connect with and learn from others.
I&amp;rsquo;m a Program Analyst for the Federal Government (views here are entirely my own), and I have a background in health policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>